torrentsafe.com 2019-06-08

# Torrent Safe | Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The following information is provided to your by TorrentSafe, it describes how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the data provided to our users while accessing and using TorrentSafe. By accessing or using this website and its functions you acknowledge that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service agrement on this website.

**Information Collected by TorrentSafe**  
In order to provide our service, TorrentSafe collects both non-personally identifiable and personally identifiable information about end users. Personally Identifiable Information This may include information such as your IP address, browser type and language, pages viewed, the date and time. TorrentSafe will not collect your password or payment information you have supplied or saved.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell or provide personal information to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services. We will only retain the information that is necessary to properly use the site.

**Cookies**  
Cookies identify your computer through your browser to enable our systems to recognize each user. TorrentSafe uses cookies to operate our service. These cookies do not collect personal information. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, in order to use all the functions of TorrentSafe cookie must be enabled.

**Third-party service-based information**  
TorrentSafe reserves the right to participate in affiliate advertising programs designed to provide a means to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to third party advertisers. 

**E-mail Communications**  
If you choose to provide your email address, TorrentSafe will communicate with you about your user services. By providing your email address you consent to receiving such communications by e-mail. In addition, if you contact us, we may retain a record of your contact information and your message to ensure a proper response to you. We may also send e-mails with service updates, news or promotions. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please opt out at any time or contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Use of TorrentSafe by Children** TorrentSafe is not intended for children. If you are under 18, you may use the Site and Services only with the supervision of your parent or guardian.

**Variation**

TorrentSafe at any time may revise, add-to, or emit sections of this user agreement. These revised terms and conditions will apply to the use of this website from the date of the publication on this site. Please check this page regularly to ensure you are familiar with the current version.

**Entire Agreement**

This Privacy Policy along with the user agreement and terms of service constitute the entire agreement between you and TorrentSafe in relation to your use of this website, and supersede all previous agreements in respect of your use of this website.
